[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: This series is created solely for entertainment purposes.
All individuals, behaviors, places, and events depicted are entirely fictional,
with no intention to represent or reference any organizations, departments, occupations, or individuals]
Can I go with you?
I forgot to bring my umbrella.
If I say you can't,
will you go away?
Why are you teasing me like that?
I'm just kidding.
I want you to know
that I didn't want you to go far away.
At last,
I finally get to see the girl under the yellow umbrella
I've always dreamt of.
[North Star Entertainment]
[Presents]
[Third Person]
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The question that's trapped in my heart♫
♫Maybe it's time for you to do your part♫
♫Choose the one your heart truly desires♫
♫Before the last raindrop falls, don't make me shed another tear♫
Can I go with you?
I forgot to bring my umbrella.
Thank you
for letting me go with you.
Ever since I lost my memories four years ago,
I've dreamt of the time I fell in love.
I don't know if it's a memory or just my imagination.
But the dream world
is more interesting than reality.
Kiiro,
aren't you bored
of eating the same food
and staying in the same place every day?
What am I even asking?
What choice do you have?
But it's alright,
you aren't stuck here alone.
I'm stuck here too.
Whatever.
We don't have a choice anyway.
Others might run to exercise,
to focus,
or to compete.
But I run because I don't know what else to do.
I run to pass the time
so that I can go back to sleep and dream.
I never thought...
my dream would be right in front of me.
Is that all?
Are there any apples missing?
Better not go missing again.
I mean...
the apples.
Without your help,
it might've been a lot harder for me.
Thank you so much.
It's alright.
No trouble at all.
Let me help you, too.
Then...
Can I go with you?
Of course,
wherever you're going,
I'll take you there.
I also don't want you to get wet.
Then...
Why is...
the world suddenly less dull?
I think the rain has stopped.
Thank you
for walking with me this far.
Please... excuse me.
Here.
Oh!
Are you alright?
I should be asking you that.
[Emergency Room]
Please collect your medicine that way.
- Thank you. - Yes.
She's the owner of that flowerpot.
Well...
you seem fine now.
I'll leave then.
What a waste of time.
Hey,
aren't you going to take responsibility for hurting her?
And who told you to walk around there?
How was I supposed to know
someone would be walking by?
And you think it's okay to throw a flowerpot like that?
It's my flowerpot.
Whatever I do with it is none of your business!
But you threw it at a person!
Then why were you walking there?!
Please stop.
I'm fine...
See?
She said she's fine.
So stop sticking your nose in.
I'm really okay now.
Let's go to the police station.
Let the police handle this.
I thought you'd be angrier,
but...
you asked for the flowerpot that fell on you as compensation?
Don't you want compensation for wasting your time?
What about you?
Hm?
You're the one whose time was wasted
because you helped me.
You are the one helping me.
Without you,
I would've gotten injured.
Then that's alright.
We helped each other out.
And this plant, too.
It's not even dead yet.
But she threw it away?
From the looks of it, it might not survive.
I don't even know what plant this is.
It's a rose plant.
If it survives...
The flowers would be beautiful.
You want roses that much?
I want another chance.
Everyone who has made mistakes
would probably want another chance.
If they're sorry
and have already apologized,
I'm willing to forgive them.
How kind of you.
Not really.
I wanted another chance as well.
Both me...
and the rose.
How sad...
I couldn't understand anything you said.
Then would you like to listen a little longer?
My condo isn't far from here,
so can you bring this rose plant...
to its home?
You're... all wet.
Would you like to come inside to shower and change?
Normally...
do people go into a stranger's room after meeting them only once?
You're right...
I'm Chris.
What's your name?
I'm Sun.
Nice to meet you, Sun.
I'll be in your care.
Nice to meet you, too.
Chris...
Feel free to use the bathroom.
Wash your hair, too.
Bangkok is full of pollution and dust.
Okay.
Here's some hot cocoa.
It'll help warm you up.
Thank you.
But this is Thailand.
It'll only be cold for a few days before it gets hot again.
But...
you're shivering.
I'd better drink something warm.
I've never had cocoa like this before.
How did you make this?
It's so delicious.
It's my secret recipe.
If you want to have this,
you can only get it here.
I like your shampoo.
It smells so good.
It actually is.
I like this smell when it's on you, too.
[Nadear]
Ow...
Sun...
I'm sorry. Are you hurt?
Let me see.
Whoa.
Does it hurt?
I forgive you.
It's okay.
[Nadear]
Don't you need to head back now?
They're calling you.
Chris,
can I ask you something personal?
What is it?
Do you have a partner?
I... don't have a partner.
[Third Person]
Chris.
Chris?
You went quiet after I said I don't have a partner.
What were you thinking about?
Uh, it's nothing.
Thinking of something lewd, aren't you?
No!
I really wasn't thinking about anything like that.
But your reaction tells me otherwise.
Well,
what were you thinking about?
I want to know your lewd thoughts.
I forgot.
I have a meeting today.
Then...
I won't trouble you any longer.
I'll take my leave.
The rain has stopped as well.
Does that mean...
if I don't have work
and it's still raining,
you're not going to leave?
Yes?
Just kidding.
But this is the first time
I want to skip my meeting,
and...
want it to rain all day.
Take this with you
in case it rains again.
Thank you.
Um...
Sun.
Yes?
Thank you for today.
Then...
please excuse me.
Will you come running again tomorrow?
I usually run every day.
That's great.
I want to run tomorrow as well.
Hello, Kiiro.
You'd definitely be jealous of me
if you knew what happened today.
You're back, Chris?
I called you several times.
Why didn't you answer?
I haven't made a reservation yet.
Where do you think...
we should go celebrate our tenth anniversary?
Do you have a place you want to go?
I'm fine with anywhere.
Pick wherever you like.
You know
there's only one place I like.
Our place.
[Third Person Bar - Bistro]
Oh, Chris,
long time no see.
Doing well?
Yeah, Nan.
I'm fine, as usual.
Nadear took good care of you, huh?
She just asked me to reserve a table.
But seriously,
don't you guys ever eat anywhere else?
If we eat here, all three of us make money.
Isn't that good?
Or you don't want it?
Want to pull out your shares, then?
I'm just teasing you.
You only have to say the word,
and I'll reserve a VIP table
with a special menu
for my shareholders, sisters, and family.
Alright, I'll lead the way.
Nadear...
Are your parents here yet?
If I tell you they're already here,
will you stop frowning?
Congratulations, dear.
Time really flies, huh?
Before we know it,
you two have been dating for a decade.
Look at your mother and me.
We've been together for thirty years now.
And that isn't easy, dear.
Then Chris and I will be together for over thirty years.
Is that true, Chris?
Of course...
Hearing you say that,
I feel relieved.
I have only one daughter
who I love and cherish dearly.
Your father and I
are getting quite old now.
If one day we pass away,
I'm just scared that Nadear would be all alone.
Dearie...
why are you saying sad things on her anniversary?
Chris already said
they'll be together for over thirty years.
Thank you so much, Chris,
for taking care of Nadear.
I know my daughter
is very stubborn.
But if you're with her,
her father and I can rest easy.
But I'd be even more at ease
if you made it official.
You've been dating for ten years now.
You live in the same house
and work at the same place.
When are you going to get married?
Nan, the influencer at that table
is making a big fuss.
She said I gave her the wrong order,
but I wrote down exactly what she ordered.
Wawah,
if I could split myself in two,
I'd help you with that.
Our head chef is getting complaints
because the food hasn't been served yet.
Alright,
you go calm her down first.
I'll go help out in the kitchen, then I'll come help you.
If I could do that, why would I come to you in the first place?!
Wawah,
where is that influencer sitting?
Excuse me,
my waitress told me you got the wrong order?
I ordered baked crab with roe and vermicelli.
But I got baked crab and vermicelli.
I already ate it,
so I knew the crab had no roe in it.
I'd like you to remake the dish.
Because...
I got the wrong dish.
But you really ordered baked crab and vermicelli.
You didn't say, "Crab with roe."
Are you saying I forgot what I said?
Then let me offer you a solution.
We'll check the security footage.
If our waitress is at fault,
we'll take full responsibility.
So you're going to blame the customer, huh?!
You're going to believe her?!
I'm your customer!
I'm sorry for wasting your time.
We'll remake your dish for you.
As an apology,
we won't charge you for this dish.
Excuse me,
are you the owner of this restaurant?
Yes.
No wonder...
you handled things better than other employees.
Why did you listen to the customer?
We didn't even know if it was our fault.
I know you want to do what's right,
and you don't want to hurt her feelings.
But trying to find out the truth is a waste of time.
And if the customer is dissatisfied,
she might write a bad review, which would make things worse.
Even though we're not wrong?
Taking the blame is another way to resolve an issue.
So you think I can't handle this on my own?
This is my restaurant as well.
But you haven't worked in a long time.
You wouldn't understand the customers.
Trust me, alright?
Don't let this ruin our special day.
Let's go back to lunch.
Mom and Dad are waiting.
I can only go, can't I?
[Happy 10th Anniversary, Chris and Nadear]
- Mm, so delicious. - Is it good?
There's salted egg.
Cholesterol, huh?
You won't be lonely anymore.
Come live with me, little rose.
How did you know it's a rose plant?
Have you grown one before?
I did when I was younger,
but...
after I moved, I didn't have any.
Do you think it'll survive?
It depends on...
how you treat it.
Treating a plant
is like treating a person.
If you don't take good care of it,
don't water
or cherish it,
it won't work out.
But since this is the rose plant you saved,
I'll work it out.
Because I want to stay close.
The rose plant would be happy to hear that.
You're the one who should be happy.
The one I want to stay close to
is you, Chris.
Can't you do this for my parents
every once in a while?
Why did you have to run away?
Did you know I had to lie to them
that you were feeling sick, so you couldn't see them off to their car?
You're good at lying anyway, aren't you?
Just like when you lied to our customer.
Is this really your excuse
for not seeing my parents off?
I'm not making excuses.
But you're being sarcastic.
That's not okay...
Then what can I do?
Can I tell you the truth?
I don't want to see your parents off
because I feel ashamed.
I can't face your parents.
I can't lie to them any longer.
Chris...
I can't take this anymore.
Pretending we're in love for your parents
won't put their minds at ease,
so you can live your life freely.
Do you know why?
Because if we're still together,
we'll always fight.
Do you have someone else?
Why shouldn't I?
We broke up a long time ago.
[Third Person]
I'm sorry...
I said mean things to you today.
I'll change.
It won't happen again.
Will you forgive me?
Please, Chris...?
Okay, okay.
Alright.
I love you because you're so kind.
I'm sorry.
I know your body is rejecting this,
but I just want to hug you.
I'll wait...
until you feel better.
Until we can hug each other.
But it's been four years now, Nadear.
No matter how long I have to wait,
I won't give up.
I'll make you want to hug me.
And don't go hugging anyone else before me.
But you couldn't do that, could you?
You can't even stand
touching anyone else.
Your past trauma
made your body reject physical touch.
It's a defense mechanism caused by your trauma.
If you heal from that trauma,
your body
will slowly stop rejecting physical contact.
What if it suddenly stopped rejecting?
Can you touch Nadear now?
Not Nadear,
but a woman I met by accident.
When we were close,
I didn't feel uncomfortable.
I didn't feel awkward like when I was with Nadear...
or with any other woman.
What did you feel when you were close to her?
I wanted to stop,
but I couldn't.
I couldn't stop myself.
Do you like her?
I tried not to have any feelings for her.
Then what will you do next?
What can I do?
You know I still have to live with Nadear.
But you two already broke up.
I can't tell anyone that, Doctor.
From an outsider's perspective,
we'd still have to be together.
I just don't want her to
get tangled up in this mess.
Let me ask you something.
If you could touch Nadear,
would anything change?
Before we broke up,
I already told Nadear that this isn't about physical contact.
Even if we'd had sex,
we would've broken up anyway.
Nadear and I really aren't compatible.
Then...
why don't you talk to Nadear about this?
If that woman can help you feel better,
Nadear will understand.
And what if she doesn't?
I know
that you feel bad for Nadear,
but I want you to be happy.
This is your life.
Are you going to let guilt stop you from being happy?
Sun.
Yes?
I'm sorry,
I got the wrong person.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
You broke your promise.
Didn't you say you'd run here yesterday?
What?
Did you run here yesterday?
I probably... assumed
that we'd meet here.
I'm sorry...
I had errands yesterday.
What if tomorrow...
I'm not free tomorrow.
But I'm free today.
Are you good at gardening?
Didn't you say you knew how to grow plants?
You said you took care of a rose plant.
That was a long time ago,
and my father helped me too.
If I have to do it alone,
I don't know if it'll work out.
Then...
Let's learn together.
Didn't you say you knew how to grow plants?
Well, if I said I didn't know how to grow plants,
would I get to come with you?
You don't have to lie
to come with me.
You can just say you want to come, and I'll let you come with me.
Hello.
What plant would you like?
I'll get the soil and the rest of the plants
for you.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I thought you only wanted to grow roses,
but you wanted to be a cook as well?
I've wanted to pick ingredients straight from the garden for a while now.
- Mm... - So...
Don't you want to grow something as well, Chris?
I'm not that into growing plants,
but I like the smell of petrichor.
It feels refreshing.
Then that means...
you like the smell of bacteria.
Hm?
The smell of petrichor
comes from plants' natural oils.
When it rains,
these oils mix with chemicals in the soil,
especially geosmin
from bacteria,
creating the refreshing smell you like.
They say this chemical can make you feel calm
and relieve stress.
You're such a nerd.
Do you like nerds, then?
Are you alright?
We ran through the rain yesterday,
and today we ran through the sprinklers.
How eventful.
But this shouldn't have happened.
They could see that we were there,
so why did they turn on the sprinklers?
I'll talk to them.
Chris.
Do you smell that?
Mm.
The smell...
of bacteria.
It actually helps relieve stress, huh?
It's not because of the petrichor, though.
Are you saying it's because of me?
You're quite a narcissist, huh?
Am I wrong, then?
If it weren't for you,
I would've been so stressed my head would have exploded.
I defused the bomb for you,
so you don't have to be angry anymore.
They probably didn't mean to make their customers wet.
How can you be so optimistic?
Maybe it's because I've been through terrible things.
If I don't look at the bright side,
I might not be able to move forward.
Let's get our plants.
[Third Person]
Take a shower right away
before you get sick.
It's funny
how we got wet on different days.
But it won't be funny if you get sick.
I won't be.
I'll take a shower now.
Hey!
What're you doing?
Didn't you tell me to take a shower right away?
Well, you don't have to rush that much.
You have to survive
so we can be together for a long time.
I want to see beautiful roses from you too.
If you're done unwrapping,
you can put it there.
Oh!
Hey,
get back inside.
What is it, Chris?
Someone might take photos of you.
Phone cameras have such powerful zoom nowadays.
Just say you're worried about me.
No need to explain this much.
Don't worry anymore.
No one can see me in this room
except the one I want them to.
I'll have to save the plants.
Chris.
Oh!
You've been out here for a while now.
Is there something on your mind?
Should we head back inside?
I'm fine outside.
I like looking at the plants.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Then let me introduce you to them.
This is Ri.
If it sprouts more leaves,
I'll promote it to Ri-ri.
And this is...
Li.
If it grows a bit more, I'll promote it too.
Promote it to Li-li?
Yeah.
And these are...
Oo-oo-oo.
Oo-oo-oo?
Yeah.
That's a cute name.
Make yourself at home.
I'll wait inside.
[Nadear]
Jeen...
Chris has never been like this before.
I don't know what to do anymore.
What happened, Nadear?
I feel like I'm about to lose her.
Can you help me, Jeen?
I can't lose her.
I want Chris to love me like she used to.
Are you a dancer?
Is that an insult?
No.
Well...
You seem to enjoy music.
Are you a DJ?
Wrong.
Then...
a model?
Try again.
You know what my job is.
Are you a doctor?
You're smart.
No, you are.
I don't really work as a doctor much anymore.
I'm more on the management side now.
I co-own a clinic with my friend.
Then...
can you look at my face for me, Doc?
Are there any adjustments needed?
You're already pretty.
Your skin is glowing.
Your features are well-balanced.
Your under-eyes are full and plump.
No need for fillers.
Your chin...
is naturally beautiful.
As for your lips...
very kissable.
It's alright if you can't hug me.
I just want you to stay by my side.
What's wrong?
I was in a car accident several years ago.
Does it still hurt?
My doctor said the accident made me reject physical contact.
It's a defense mechanism in response to trauma.
The trauma here?
I thought physical touch could help you recover.
I don't want you to be in this terrible relationship.
Follow your heart, Chris.
You make the person you're with feel seen.
That's the reason
I want to be your friend.
Who gave you this?
A friend.
I don't want to see you in pain
or see you sad anymore,
because I love you!
Am I wrong for that?
Friends don't kiss, do they?
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The question that's trapped in my heart♫
♫Maybe it's time for you to do your part♫
♫Choose the one your heart truly desires♫
♫Before the last raindrop falls, don't make me shed another tear♫